[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "You want me to get drunk and talk to a peacock?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "me", "to", "get", "drunk", "and", "talk", "to", "a", "peacock", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "His movie career.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "movie", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec Baldwin"]}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "What could be more, what could more of a preposterous waste of our time than that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "be", "more", ",", "what", "could", "more", "of", "a", "preposterous", "waste", "of", "our", "time", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", ",", "WP", "MD", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Alec Baldwin, outspoken, unapologetic, and very, very funny.", "answer_tokens": ["Alec", "Baldwin", ",", "outspoken", ",", "unapologetic", ",", "and", "very", ",", "very", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Do you think he's actually going to start commissioning those kind of dreamy inspirational projects which will get the whole world gasping and all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "actually", "going", "to", "start", "commissioning", "those", "kind", "of", "dreamy", "inspirational", "projects", "which", "will", "get", "the", "whole", "world", "gasping", "and", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I'm hopeful that he will and I'm -- and that hope is based on the notion that presidents, regardless of party, have more flexibility or perceived flexibility in their second term because there is no possibility for re-election.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "hopeful", "that", "he", "will", "and", "I", "'m", "--", "and", "that", "hope", "is", "based", "on", "the", "notion", "that", "presidents", ",", "regardless", "of", "party", ",", "have", "more", "flexibility", "or", "perceived", "flexibility", "in", "their", "second", "term", "because", "there", "is", "no", "possibility", "for", "re-election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"], "PERCENT": ["110 percent"]}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "The question is, can you speak for 10 seconds without alienating your base?", "question_tokens": ["The", "question", "is", ",", "can", "you", "speak", "for", "10", "seconds", "without", "alienating", "your", "base", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Now the conservative base needs to know that Rick Perry stands with them 110 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "the", "conservative", "base", "needs", "to", "know", "that", "Rick", "Perry", "stands", "with", "them", "110", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "I mean, when you see, Alec, when you someone like Arnold Schwarzenegger become governor of California, you must think to yourself, I could do at least as good a job as that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "when", "you", "see", ",", "Alec", ",", "when", "you", "someone", "like", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "become", "governor", "of", "California", ",", "you", "must", "think", "to", "yourself", ",", "I", "could", "do", "at", "least", "as", "good", "a", "job", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "You'd be reading my mind if you said that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'d", "be", "reading", "my", "mind", "if", "you", "said", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec", "Arnold Schwarzenegger"], "LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Has part of you always harbored the possibility that you could one day run for the presidency?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "part", "of", "you", "always", "harbored", "the", "possibility", "that", "you", "could", "one", "day", "run", "for", "the", "presidency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, I think that it's something that I used to think about a long, long time ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "something", "that", "I", "used", "to", "think", "about", "a", "long", ",", "long", "time", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "DT", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Who do you fancy?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "fancy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, I think that the only thing I can day about that is I have some personal favorites, I have people that were nominated that I was excited about and some that I was -- like anybody -- I was maybe perplexed by, if you will.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "only", "thing", "I", "can", "day", "about", "that", "is", "I", "have", "some", "personal", "favorites", ",", "I", "have", "people", "that", "were", "nominated", "that", "I", "was", "excited", "about", "and", "some", "that", "I", "was", "--", "like", "anybody", "--", "I", "was", "maybe", "perplexed", "by", ",", "if", "you", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oscars"]}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "I think they should both -- if they were to win best actress and best actor, to me, that just immediately gives the Oscars that kind of heavyweight glamour, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "should", "both", "--", "if", "they", "were", "to", "win", "best", "actress", "and", "best", "actor", ",", "to", "me", ",", "that", "just", "immediately", "gives", "the", "Oscars", "that", "kind", "of", "heavyweight", "glamour", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "NN", "CC", "JJS", "NN", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, to the extent that the Oscars, I mean, sometimes those votes as you well know even in recent history, they swing in a very wide track.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "the", "extent", "that", "the", "Oscars", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "sometimes", "those", "votes", "as", "you", "well", "know", "even", "in", "recent", "history", ",", "they", "swing", "in", "a", "very", "wide", "track", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", "POS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What was she like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "she", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "You know, she is -- Meryl's -- I'm not going to say anything fresh about her or new that hasn't been said by countless other, you know, more formidable, leading men than I'll ever be.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "she", "is", "--", "Meryl", "'s", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "say", "anything", "fresh", "about", "her", "or", "new", "that", "has", "n't", "been", "said", "by", "countless", "other", ",", "you", "know", ",", "more", "formidable", ",", "leading", "men", "than", "I", "'ll", "ever", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Was it really Tina Fey's fault, Alec?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "really", "Tina", "Fey", "'s", "fault", ",", "Alec", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "No, of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tina Fey", "Alec"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Angry?", "question_tokens": ["Angry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "You know, I was very embarrassed and I was very upset because I thought, you know, first of all, that there were people -- I mean, the joke obviously when I got off the plane was there were four other guys Twittering from their cell phones as I was getting kicked off the plane for using my cell phone.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "very", "embarrassed", "and", "I", "was", "very", "upset", "because", "I", "thought", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "that", "there", "were", "people", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "joke", "obviously", "when", "I", "got", "off", "the", "plane", "was", "there", "were", "four", "other", "guys", "Twittering", "from", "their", "cell", "phones", "as", "I", "was", "getting", "kicked", "off", "the", "plane", "for", "using", "my", "cell", "phone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Would you ever fly American again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "fly", "American", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I guess if they gave us -- if they gave us a device on board that we could play Words With Friends while we were flying on the plane with other people on the plane -- play words with friends with other people on board.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "if", "they", "gave", "us", "--", "if", "they", "gave", "us", "a", "device", "on", "board", "that", "we", "could", "play", "Words", "With", "Friends", "while", "we", "were", "flying", "on", "the", "plane", "with", "other", "people", "on", "the", "plane", "--", "play", "words", "with", "friends", "with", "other", "people", "on", "board", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec"]}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What could be more of a preposterous waste of our time than that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "be", "more", "of", "a", "preposterous", "waste", "of", "our", "time", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "We have got the message loud and clear, Alec, although the trouble was hugely entertaining.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "got", "the", "message", "loud", "and", "clear", ",", "Alec", ",", "although", "the", "trouble", "was", "hugely", "entertaining", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "``", "CD", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Do you get more or less fun from Twitter than you do from \"30 Rock\"?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "more", "or", "less", "fun", "from", "Twitter", "than", "you", "do", "from", "``", "30", "Rock", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "CD", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Oh, I get infinitely more fun from \"30 Rock\" than anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "get", "infinitely", "more", "fun", "from", "``", "30", "Rock", "''", "than", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "This is the perfect woman for you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "perfect", "woman", "for", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, Yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "I was about to ask you how many times you have been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "about", "to", "ask", "you", "how", "many", "times", "you", "have", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "The past is just a blur to me now, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "past", "is", "just", "a", "blur", "to", "me", "now", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "You have a child?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "child", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I just -- my wife gave birth to a little baby girl two months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--", "my", "wife", "gave", "birth", "to", "a", "little", "baby", "girl", "two", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "How long ago?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Two months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Does she sleep well, your child?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "sleep", "well", ",", "your", "child", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "She doesn't sleep too badly.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "does", "n't", "sleep", "too", "badly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Have I thought about having more kids?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "thought", "about", "having", "more", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "I have to ask you this, Alec, because I ask everyone this: outside of children and marriage and so on, what has been the single greatest moment of your life, the moment that if I could relive it for you right now, you would ask to relive it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "ask", "you", "this", ",", "Alec", ",", "because", "I", "ask", "everyone", "this", ":", "outside", "of", "children", "and", "marriage", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "has", "been", "the", "single", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", ",", "the", "moment", "that", "if", "I", "could", "relive", "it", "for", "you", "right", "now", ",", "you", "would", "ask", "to", "relive", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "DT", ":", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "There's a few of them.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "few", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec"]}}]